ubiome.com 2016-03-14

# uBiome Website and Services

   uBiome Website and Services
                   Privacy Statement
This document governs how we use your data for commercial purposes
including collection of data on our website and during use of our services
via our website and other online avenues such as mobile apps. The
document gives us broad discretion to use your data for a variety of
purposes, including sharing it with third parties. Please read this document
carefully for the details.
uBiome Services and the uBiome website are provided by uBiome, Inc.
(“uBiome”), whose principal place of business is at 1700 Fourth Street #219
San Francisco CA 94158.
This Privacy Statement is for www.ubiome.com, register.ubiome.com, other
websites operated by uBiome as well as mobile applications provided by
uBiome. We are committed to providing you a secure, user-controlled
environment for the use of our Services. At the same time, you share
responsibility for maintaining privacy and security - for example, by keeping
your password secure.
Personal Information We Collect
"Personal Information" is information that can be used to identify you, either
alone or in combination with other information. uBiome collects and stores
the following types of Personal Information:
•  "Registration Information" is the information you provide about yourself
   when registering for and/or purchasing our Services (e.g. name, email,
   address, user ID and password, and payment information).
•  "Phenotypic Information" is information regarding the Phenotype (e.g. the
   As, Ts, Cs, and Gs at particular locations) in the microbiome sample),
   generated through processing of your samples by uBiome or by its
   contractors, successors, and assignees; or otherwise processed by
   and/or contributed to uBiome.
•  "Self-Reported Information" is all information about yourself, including
   your disease conditions, other health-related information, personal traits,

  ethnicity, family history, and other information that you enter into
  surveys, forms, or features while signed in to your uBiome account. Self-
  Reported Information is included in uBiome Research only if you have
  given consent as described in the applicable Consent Document.
• "User Content" is all information, data, text, software, music, audio,
  photographs, graphics, video, messages, or other materials - other than
  Phenotypic Information or Self-Reported Information - generated by
  users of uBiome Services and transmitted, whether publicly or privately,
  to or through uBiome.
• "Web Behavior Information" is information on how you use the uBiome
  website (e.g. browser type, domains, pageviews) collected through log
  files, cookies, and web beacon technology.
How We Use Your Information
• uBiome collects Personal Information from you for all purposes
  necessary to ensure the regular operation of your account and/or
  availability of our Services. These include, among other things, providing
  you with our Services; improving our Services and/or offering new
  products or services to you; informing you about events; inviting you to
  participate in specific research projects, contacting you to obtain
  testimonials or for other promotional purposes; performing quality control
  activities; conducting other R&D; and, upon your authorization,
  conducting uBiome Research.
• We use Registration Information to enable your purchase, inform you
  when your Phenotypic Information is available to you, provide you with
  customer service, manage our Services, and authenticate your website
  visits and usage.
• We may disclose to third parties, and/or use in our Services,
  "Aggregated Phenotypic and Self-Reported Information", which is
  Phenotypic and Self-Reported Information that has been stripped of
  Registration Information and combined with data from a number of other
  users sufficient to minimize the possibility of exposing individual-level
  information while still providing scientific evidence of greater scientific
  import.
• If you have given consent for your Phenotypic and Self-Reported
  Information to be used in uBiome Research as described in the
  applicable Consent Document, we may include such information in
  Aggregated Phenotypic and Self-Reported Information intended to be
  published in peer-reviewed scientific journals. If you have given consent
  to participate in uBiome Research, we may also allow research
  contractors to access your individual-level Phenotypic and/or Self-
  Reported Information onsite at uBiome’s offices for the purpose of

   conducting scientific research, provided that all such research
   contractors will be supervised by uBiome and subject to uBiome’s
   access rules and guidelines.
•  If you do not give consent for your Phenotypic and Self-Reported
   Information to be used in uBiome Research, we may still use your
   Phenotypic and/or Self-Reported Information for other purposes, which
   may include disclosure of Aggregated Phenotypic and Self-Reported
   Information to third-party non-profit and/or commercial research partners
   who will not publish that information in a peer-reviewed scientific journal.
•  Except as otherwise set forth herein, we will never release your
   individual-level Phenotypic and/or Self-Reported Information to a third
   party without asking for and receiving your explicit consent to do so,
   unless required by law.
•  We use Web Behavior Information to track and monitor aggregate usage
   of our website, for R&D, for quality control, to improve our Services,
   and/or to target advertising for our products and services, and if you
   have given consent to participate in uBiome Research as described in
   the applicable Consent Document, your Web Behavior Information may
   be used and disclosed to third parties in aggregate form for uBiome
   Research intended to be published in peer-reviewed scientific journals.
•  If you do not give consent to participate in uBiome Research, we may
   still use your Web Behavior Information for R&D purposes as described
   above, which may include disclosure of aggregated Web Behavior
   Information to third-party non-profit and/or commercial research partners
   who will not publish that information in a peer-reviewed scientific journal.
•  We give you the ability to share your Phenotypic Information with other
   uBiome customers through sharing features.
Information Disclosure
We will not disclose your individual-level Personal Information to any third
party, except under the following circumstances:
•  Partners or service providers (e.g. our contracted phenotyping laboratory
   or credit card processors) use and/or store the information in order to
   provide you with uBiome's Services.
•  If you have consented for research, research contractors may access
   your individual-level Phenotypic and Self-Reported Information on-site at
   uBiome's offices for the purpose of scientific research, provided that all
   such research contractors will be supervised by uBiome and subject to
   uBiome's access rules and guidelines.
•  We are required to do so by law.

•  You have provided explicit consent for us to do so.
Your Choices
•  Contribution of Personal Information other than Registration Information
   is voluntary and permission-based.
•  Whether to give consent for uBiome to use your Phenotypic and Self-
   Reported Information for uBiome Research is voluntary.
•  Providing Self-Reported Information through surveys, forms, or features
   is voluntary.
•  At your written request we will close your account. As a result, all
   Phenotypic Information will be removed from the account and will no
   longer be accessible. uBiome will not use your Phenotypic Information in
   new research that starts thirty (30) days or more after account closure.
   We cannot remove Phenotypic Information that has previously been used
   for published research or shared with external collaborators before
   account closure.
How to Contact Us
Questions about this Summary, our Privacy Statement, or about uBiome's
handling    of   your   Personal     Information   may   be   emailed    to
privacy@uBiome.com, or sent to:
Privacy Administrator
uBiome, Inc.
1700 Fourth Street #219
San Francisco CA 94158
